It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
Become more beautiful.
も っと綺麗になって
is that so?
そうですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
As always, so cute.
相変わらずね、可愛くて
How have you been?
元気してた?
I was doing well.
元気してました
How have you been?
元 気してた?
Where have you been to lately?
最近はどこ遊びに行ったり?
I went to an art museum.
美術館に行きました
Art museum?
美術館?
yes.
はい
Art museum.
美術館
That's amazing.
すごいね
what kind?
どんな?
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
Is it like a painting or something?
絵画とかそういう?
It's a painting.
絵画ですね
It's an intelligent interior.
知的なインテリアね
I haven't been to an art museum recently.
最近行ってなかったね、美術館
That's right, I like it.
そうなんだ、好きなんだ
Yes, I like it.
そうですね、好きです
Did you go with your boyfriend?
彼氏と行ったの?
No, I don't have a boyfriend.
いや、彼氏いないですよ
Since then?
あれから?
I see.
そうか
Have you not been?
行ってない?
I haven't been there.
行ってないです
Because work is my priority.
仕事の方が優先なので
Should I focus on work?
仕事に専念しちゃいけない?
I agree.
そうですね
You're doing a great job right now, aren't you?
今すごい仕事してるんだよね?
that's right.
そうです
that's right?
そうです?
What are you doing?
何してるんですか?
It's a model.
モデルです
What activities have you done recently?
最近どんな活動をしたの?
Recently, I was filming a drama.
最近は、ドラマの撮影してました
Is there a drama coming out?
ドラマ出てるの?
It's a short story though.
短編ですけど
Wow, that's amazing.
えー、すごいね
Are you also an actress?
女優もやってる?
Ah, it feels like a sword.
あ、剣って感じですね
Sword row.
剣行
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you aiming to become an actress?
女優目指してるの?
Have you gotten used to the camera yet?
もう なんか、カメラ慣れてきたの?
I'm more used to it than before.
前よりは慣れました
I've made more friends than before.
前よりは友達でできたんだけど
Recommended.
おすすめです
Have you had an edge recently?
最近エッジした?
I haven't, not at all.
してないです、全然
Haven't you?
してない?
Yeah.
うん
So, since then?
じゃあ、あれ以来?
that's right.
そうです
Just the previous photo.
前の撮影だけです
After a long time.
久々に
Well, check it out after a while.
じゃあ、久々にチェック
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's like an internal mirror that you open by yourself.
自分で開いて、内鏡みたいな
It's like this.
こんな感じ
fault.
あら
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You can see this on the stairs.
これ、階段とかで見られちゃうよ
terrible.
やばい
Please do it.
しなさいね
I'm going to watch a lot today too.
いっぱい見ちゃうよ、今日も
Full.
い っぱい
Oh, that's so scary.
あ、めちゃくちゃ怖い
I think I fell asleep.
寝てきちゃったんじゃないかな
I fell asleep.
寝てきちゃった
Looks embarrassing.
恥ずかしそう
pure white.
真っ白
Well, this is it.
もうね、これね
Ssssss
すっ
So beautiful.
ご い綺麗
You end up exercising a lot.
いっぱい運動しちゃうんだよね
sleep
寝て
It's here.
き ちゃったね
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
し そう
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あ、 恥ずかしい
This fall.
この、秋にする
It looks familiar, amazing.
見慣らしいじゃん、すごい
I went to sleep though.
寝てきましたけどね
Just sleep on your feet.
ちょっと足から寝てきて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's delicious.
おいしいです
It's amazing what you've done here.
すごいここにしちゃってるね
Now, expand your time.
さあ、時間を広げてみ
All over the body.
全身に
There's a lot in it though.
すごい入ってるけど
Come on, come on now.
さあ、もうさ、
Don't get on your knees.
ちょっと 膝立ちないで
It's amazing.
すごいしちゃってるね
Lay on your stomach, don't get on your knees.
お腹をまさま、膝立ちないで
Don't clean your stomach.
お腹を掃除しないで
What happened?
何が出てきちゃったの?
I fell asleep on my feet.
足を寝ちゃった
Did you fall asleep on your feet?
足を寝ちゃったの?
It didn't come out the other day.
この前、出なかった
That's amazing.
すごいね
This is a must-have.
必修しよう、これ
What's wrong with this?
どうしたの、これ
It had accumulated a bit, quite a lot.
ちょっと溜まってたんだよね、相当
Wasn't it accumulated?
溜まってたんじゃないの?
In hand too.
こっちも手に
It feels good.
気持ちいいですよ
amazing.
すごい
That seems really far away.
すごい遠そうだね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Isn't that amazing, Trego?
すごいじゃない、トレゴ
It came out great.
すごい出てきたね
Let's sit and lick together.
一緒に座らなめよう
Hey, here's your butt.
ちょっと こっちお尻を
amazing.
すごい
You're soaking wet right now, kid.
すぐびしょびしょだな、お子
Soaked.
び しょびしょ
amazing.
すごい
I opened it again and sat down to give it a good look.
もう一回自分で開いて座りよく見せたね
I'm just starting to lose my patience.
ちょっともうさ、我慢できなくなってきちゃったんだからさ
Is it okay?
いいの?
This time.
今回は
Leave it like this.
このままで
Even though you hated it that much?
あんなに嫌がってたのに?
Aren't you scared?
怖くないの?
There's a lot of salt in it, and it looks delicious.
けっぱいお塩も出て、気持ちよさそうだからね
That's fine, leave it like this.
いいのね、このままで
appear?
見える?
Even if I move it?
動かしても?
What are you doing?
何してる?
Tooth drawing.
歯描き
Are you drawing your teeth?
歯描きしてるの?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
It was fun.
楽しかったね
It's still not enough though.
まだ足りないんだけど
Is it not enough?
足りないの?
I really don't have enough.
本当に足りないんだけど
I don't know until I see it.
見ちゃわからんわ
Well, you won't know until you see it.
ね え、見ちゃわからんわ
Thank you very much.
せっかくね
But.
だけどね
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
While drawing your teeth?
歯描き中に?
yeah?
ん?
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Pen it.
ペンして
Did you put it on the pen?
ペ ン上にした?
Tooth drawing.
歯描き
What about behind?
後 ろは?
I drew my teeth.
歯描きしました
Hey, see you later.
ねえじゃん、またね
Oh, that's amazing.
あぁ、すっごい
Let's have a look.
見てもらおう
So far down there.
あんなに下のに
Ah, amazing.
あぁ、すごい
That's already it.
もうそんな
a,
あ、
Let's do this.
こう しとこう
That's right, good at it.
そうそう、上手
Now, strain it thoroughly.
さあ、グーッとこしとく
If this were the case, I would have been trembling.
これだったらね、プルプルしてたね
Jiggly.
プ ルプル
good?
いい?
With your mouth.
お口で
Can I cum in your mouth?
お口の中出していい?
Shall we go?
いくよ?
Ah, it came out great.
あぁ、すごい出た
Do you understand?
わかる?
Yeah.
うん
Get it and let it out.
手に入れて出してくれ
A lot came out.
いっぱい出たね
Yeah, a lot.
うん、いっぱい
Hey, it's nice to have a catchphrase.
ちょっと、 口文句もいいね
The inside is nice though.
中もいいけどね